http://www.become.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
(Effective Date 25 May 2018)
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITES OR SERVICES. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR
WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES (OTHER THAN TO READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR THE FIRST TIME), YOU AGREE TO THIS
PRIVACY POLICY.
Introduction
This Privacy Policy tells you the types of information we collect when you use our Sites or Services, how we
use that information, and the instances in which we share your information.
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term “personal data” means any information which identifies you
or which allows you to be identified when combined with other information.
Who are we?
Connexity, Inc. ("Connexity") operates online shopping websites, including Shopzilla.co.uk, bizrate.co.uk,
pricegrabber.co.uk and equivalent domains in Germany, France, and Italy (“Sites”), and provides other online
services ("Services"). As we are based in the United States of America, your information may be transmitted
to, held and processed by us there in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Connexity, Inc. is a company incorporated in the State of Delaware, USA and has its principal office
at 2120
Colorado Ave., Suite 400, Santa Monica, CA 90404.
Certain of the Services may be provided by our subsidiary Connexity Europe GmbH, with whom we may also share
your information. Connexity Europe GmbH is a company registered in Germany in accordance with the laws of
the District Court of Mannheim under company register number HRB 705360 and with its registered office at
Ruschgraben 133, 76139 Karlsruhe, Germany. “Connexity” or “Shopzilla” and the terms “we”, “us” and “our”
refer to Connexity, Inc., except where a Service is provided by Connexity Europe GmbH, in which case the
terms “we”, “us” and “our” refers to Connexity Europe GmbH.
Our data protection representative can be contacted directly here:dataprotection@connexity.com
Summary of key principles
We thought it would be helpful to set out briefly the key ways in which we use your information and how we
seek to protect privacy. Of course, we would be delighted if you read this Privacy Policy in full.
We collect and process information about you when you provide it to us, when you use our Sites or when we
are provided it by certain third parties. This information may be transmitted to, held and processed by us
in the United States of America. We pseudonymize the data that we directly collect that may be considered
personal prior to storing it.
We typically use this information for fraud prevention purposes and to improve our Sites and Services;
We may disclose this information to authorized third parties including our merchants, affiliates and
third-party service providers for these purposes;
You may object and/or withdraw consent to us processing your information in certain circumstances and at any
time opt-out of certain activities as set out below ( see section VII);
Our websites use “cookies” although you can set your browser not to accept cookies if you so wish although
this may affect your use of our Sites. We use cookies to personalize content and adverts and to analyze our
traffic. We share information about your use of our Sites with our advertising and analytics partners who
may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their
services. For more information about our use of cookies, please see our cookies
policy;
If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at Connexity, please contact us by e-mail at legal@connexity.com;
Our websites and our services are not designed or intended for use by children under 16; and
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check this policy regularly.
What information do we collect about you and where do we collect it from?
Information you give us:
We collect your information when you choose to contact us with an enquiry by mail or by
e-mail at legal@connexity.com
Information we collect about you:
We automatically collect certain information from you when you access our Sites including
your IP address and information relating to your browser, operating system, ISP, the
third-party website from which your visit originated and how you use our Sites such as the
web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.
Information we receive from other sources:
Third party merchants who use our Sites to advertise their products provide us with
information regarding any visits you make to their website via our Sites and any purchases
made by you as a result. This information includes your IP address, referring URL, browser
and/or device type and details about your order but no other personal data.
How we use & share the information collected
We use the information we collect about you for the following purposes:
to verify sales made by third party merchants as a result of them using our Sites to promote
their products and calculate our fees to them;
for fraud prevention;
to improve our Sites and Services and to carry out your requests and respond to your
enquiries;
to allow third parties to provide adverts to you on our Sites that we think may be of
interest
to you;
to advertise products to you on third party sites based on your preferences and likely
interests.
We process your information for the above purposes on the basis it is in our legitimate
interests or
consent where we ask it of you. You may object to processing by us for this reason at any
time in
accordance with section VII below.
We may disclose your information to:
Our third-party service providers who perform functions on our behalf in connection with the
operation of the Sites or Services e.g., providers who host and manage data, etc.;
Our third-party advertising partners to personalize content and adverts that appear on our Sites
and to advertise products to you on third party sites which are tailored to meet your
preferences and likely interests;
Our third-party analytics partners to analyze Site traffic and understand customer needs and
trends. We may use your anonymized information by itself or aggregate it with information we
have obtained from others to produce research reports and other information and data about
online shopping for participating merchants and other customers, as well as media and other
interested parties;
Our parent company, subsidiaries or other affiliated companies (“affiliated companies”) for
operational, marketing and promotional purposes;
A third-party purchaser of all or any of our assets, where such information is one of the assets
transferred;
A prospective seller or buyer of our business or assets; and
A third-party if we are required to do so by law, with respect to copyright and other
intellectual property infringement claims, or if we believe that such action is necessary to:
(a) fulfil a government request, including for national security or law enforcement reasons; (b)
conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal
rights or property, our Sites, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and
safety of our Sites’ users or the general public.
Transferring your information outside the European Economic Area
Some of the information we collect about you is transferred to and stored on our servers in the
United States of America. When personal data is transferred from within the EEA to any of our
affiliates outside the EEA we use the EU model clauses to ensure that the transfer is subject to
adequate safeguards in accordance with our legal obligations.
How long we store your information
The information we collect about you when you access our Sites (including referring URL, page visits,
browser and/or device type, time and date) and the information provided by our third-party merchants
is pseudonymized immediately prior to storing it, and we delete data we store after 10 years.
We store the information you provide to us when you contact us by email for a period of up to 5
years.
Cookies and similar technologies
We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you use our Sites by using
"cookies" and analogous technology. "Cookies" are small files that we place on your computer or your
Web browser memory to enable our systems to recognise your browser.
We work with third parties, including advertising companies and website analysis firms, who use
cookies to collect information about you when you visit our Sites and third-party sites about your
surfing activities. This information, collected through cookies, is typically used by our selected
third-party advertising networks to: (a) serve you with advertisements while on our Sites and
third-party sites tailored to meet your preferences and likely interests; or (b) conduct market
research and website analysis. If you do not wish to participate in this activity, please click here for options to
opt-out of advertising. You can also object to any profiling that takes place in relation to being
served with tailored advertisements in accordance with section VII below.
A couple of important notes about this opt-out guide: (1) it includes all the advertising networks
that Connexity works with, but also many that Connexity does not work with; and (2) it relies on
cookies to ensure that a given advertising network does not collect information about you (“Opt-out
Cookies”) – for a general explanation of how Opt-out Cookies work, please click here. Therefore, if you
buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete these Opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will
need to perform the opt-out task again.
You may be able to direct your internet browser not to allow cookies and you can delete existing cookies from your computer. Please note, however, some elements of our Sites will not function properly or be available to you.
For more information about our use of cookies, please see our cookies
policy.
Security of information
We use a secure server hosting location in the U, firewall protection, controlled access and encryption technology to protect your data. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us over the internet.
Your rights
Right to object to processing based on our legitimate interests:
You have the right to object to us processing your personal data on the grounds of it
being
in our legitimate interests.
Right to access, delete and correct your personal data:
You have the right to request a copy of the personal data we hold about you.
Right to be forgotten
In certain circumstances you can ask for the personal data we hold about you to be
erased
from our records.
Right to restriction of processing:
Where certain conditions apply, you may have a right to restrict the processing of
your
personal data.
Right to object to profiling:
You may object to us undertaking any profiling of you in relation to serving you with
advertisements which we think may be of interest to you by clicking here. You can
also
prevent any profiling by setting your internet browser not to allow cookies and by
using the
opt-out tool mentioned in section V above.
You may contact us with questions or if you believe you are entitled to exercise any of the
above
rights, please contact us by email at dataprotection@connexity.com.
Privacy Shield
Connexity (and its wholly-owned subsidiary, Connexity Audience, Inc.) participates in the
EU-U.S.
Privacy Shield framework. Connexity is committed to subjecting all personal data received
from EU
member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield, to the principles underlying the
Privacy Shield
(the “Principles”). To learn more about the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield program, and to view
Connexity’s
certification, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce site at
https://www.privacyshield.gov/.
Accountability for Onward Transfer
If we transfer personal data received from EU member countries, in reliance on the Privacy
Shield, to
a third party acting as a controller, we will do so consistent with any notice provided to
data
subjects and any consent they have given, and only if the third party has given us
contractual
assurances that it will (i) process the personal data for limited and specific purposes
consistent
with any consent provided by the data subjects; (ii) provide at least the same level of
privacy
protection as is required by the Principles and notify us if it makes a determination it
cannot do
so; and (iii) cease processing of the personal data or take other reasonable and appropriate
steps
to remediate if it makes such a determination. If Connexity has knowledge that a third party
acting
as a controller is processing such personal data in a way that is contrary to the
Principles,
Connexity will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop such processing.
With respect to our third-party agents, we will transfer only the personal data needed for
an agent
to deliver to Connexity the requested product or service. Furthermore, we will (i) permit
the agent
to process such personal data only for limited and specified purposes; (ii) require the
agent to
provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the Principles;
(iii) take
reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure that the agent effectively processes the personal
data
transferred in a manner consistent with Connexity’s obligations under the Principles; and
(iv)
require the agent to notify Connexity if it makes a determination that it can no longer meet
its
obligation to provide the same level of protection as is required by the Principles. Upon
receiving
notice from an agent that it can no longer meet its obligation to provide the same level of
protection as is required by the Principles, we will take reasonable and appropriate steps
to stop
and remediate unauthorized processing.
Connexity remains liable under the Principles if an agent processes personal data received
from EU
member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield, in a manner inconsistent with the
Principles,
except where Connexity is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.
Complaints
In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how your personal data is being
processed by us
or that we have not taken any action requested by you in relation to your rights set out
above, you
have the right to lodge a complaint directly with the applicable supervisory authority and
our data
protection representative.
The details for each of these contacts are:
Supervisory Authority
contact details
Data Protection Representative
contact details
Contact:
Landesbeauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit Baden-Württemberg
Connexity, Inc.
Attn: Data Protection Representative
Postal address:
Email enquiries:
bsdb@lfdi.bwl.de
dataprotection@connexity.com
Telephone:
0711 / 61 55 41 – 0
+1 (310) 571-1235
EU individuals may direct any inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield
compliance to
Connexity’s Data Protection Representative contact above. Connexity will respond within 45
days. If
you have an unresolved concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our
U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge), the International
Centre for
Dispute Resolution/American Arbitration Association, at
http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html.
Finally, as a last resort and in limited situations, you may have the possibility to engage
in
binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Panel.
Connexity’s commitments under the Privacy Shield are subject to the investigatory and
enforcement
powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission.
Children
As our Sites nor our Services are not intended for use by children under 16. Also, if you
are under 18, you should use our Sites and Services and submit information only with
involvement of a parent or guardian.
Online merchants and third-party policies
This Privacy Policy only applies to our Sites and our Services so when you access links to
online merchants or other third parties via our Sites or Services you should read their
privacy policies.
Revisions
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time to reflect our changing business practices.
We will provide you notice of any such changes by posting the new policy on our Sites or by
email if the changes are material.
If there is any conflict between the English language version of this Privacy Policy and any
translated version we may provide, the English language version will control in all
instances.
Copyright © Connexity, Inc, also trading as Shopzilla. All Rights Reserved.
© 2020 Connexity, Inc. / Become is a property of Connexity, Inc.
